<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Kolkata Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Tab 1</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tab 2</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string-array name="fragment_heading">
        <item>Places</item>
        <item>Hotels</item>
        <item>Shoping</item>
        <item>Hospital</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- TODO: Name of the places -->
    <string-array name="name_of_the_place">
        <item>Victoria Memorial</item>
        <item>Howrah Bridge</item>
        <item>Belur Math</item>
        <item>Eden Gardens</item>
        <item>Dakshineswar Kali Temple</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- TODO: Address of the places -->
    <string-array name="address_of_the_place">
        <item> Kolkata, West Bengal, India</item>
        <item>Howrah, Kolkata, West Bengal, India</item>
        <item>Belur, Kolkata, West Bengal, India</item>
        <item>Maidan, B.B.D. Bagh, Kolkata, West Bengal 700021</item>
        <item>Dakshineswar, Kolkata, West Bengal 700076</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- TODO:Description of the places -->
    <string-array name="description_of_the_palce">
        <item>
            The Victoria Memorial is a large marble building,which is considered to be the pride of Kolkata.
            Built between 1906 and 1921, it is dedicated to the memory of Queen Victoria.
            Now, it is a museum and a popular tourist spot under the Ministry of Culture.
        </item>
        <item>
            Located over the Hooghly river in West Bengal,
            Howrah Bridge or the Rabindra Setu is the main connection between Howrah and Kolkata.
            It is a cantilever bridge and is regarded as one of the busiest ones among them.
        </item>
        <item>
            Belur Mutt is the headquarters of the Ramakrishna Math and Mission, founded by Swami Vivekananda,
            the chief disciple of Ramakrishna Paramahamsa. It is situated on the west bank of Hooghly River,
            Belur, West Bengal, India. It is one of the noteworthy establishments in Kolkata.
            This temple is the focus of the Ramakrishna Movement. The temple is prominent for its architecture that embraces Hindu,
            Christian and Islamic styles and stands as an icon of unity of all religions.
        </item>
        <item>
            The Eden Gardens is a Cricket and Football multipurpose ground in Kolkata, India.
            It was established in 1864. It is the oldest cricket stadium in India.
            It will be the home ground of Eastbengal FC in ISL season 7 2020-21.
        </item>
        <item>
            Dakshineswar Kali Temple is a Hindu navaratna temple located at Dakshineswar.
            Situated on the eastern bank of the Hooghly River,
            the presiding deity of the temple is Bhavatarini, an aspect of Kali.
        </item>


    </string-array>


    <!-- TODO: Name of the hotel -->
    <string-array name="name_of_the_hotel">
        <item>The Westin Kolkata Rajarhat</item>
        <item>Pride Plaza Hotel Kolkata</item>
        <item>The Lalit Great Eastern Kolkata</item>
        <item>JW Marriott Hotel Kolkata</item>
        <item>Hyatt Regency Kolkata</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- TODO: Address of the hotel -->
    <string-array name="address_of_the_hotel">

        <item>
            Plot No CBD 2, Action Area - II,New Town,
            \nRajarhat, Kolkata 700156 India
            \nPhone: 033 4037 1234
        </item>
        <item>
            Terminus, B.G-12,1-B, New Town,
            \nRajarhat, Kolkata 700 156 India
            \nPhone: 033 45037 1254
        </item>
        <item>
            1 2 &amp; 3 Old Court House Street,
            \nKolkata 700069 India
            \nPhone: 011 4444 7474
        </item>
        <item>
            4A J.B.S Haldane Avenue,
            \nKolkata 700105 India
            \nPhone: 033 6633 0000
        </item>
        <item>
            JA - 1 Sector III Salt Lake City,
            \nKolkata 700098 India
            \nPhone: 033 6820 1234
        </item>

    </string-array>

    <!-- TODO:Description of the hotel -->
    <string-array name="description_of_the_hotel">
        <item>
            Experience a relaxing getaway situated 8 Kms from the Kolkata Airport,
            The Westin Kolkata Rajarhat is in close proximity to the International Convention Centre,
            Eco Park and the Business hub of Salt Lake &amp; Rajarhat. With the stunning Kolkata cityscape in the background,
            guests checking in to the hotel have a choice to be pampered with an invigorating massage at the Heavenly Spa by Westin,
            indulge in Westin WORKOUT facilities or simply take a refreshing dip in the outdoor pool in this calming oasis. The hotel showcases 304
        </item>
        <item>
            Finding an ideal family-friendly hotel in Kolkata (Calcutta) does not have to be difficult.
            Welcome to Pride Plaza Hotel Kolkata, a nice option for travellers like you.
            Youu will enjoy relaxing rooms that offer a flat screen TV, a minibar, and air conditioning,
            and you can stay connected during your stay as Pride Plaza Hotel Kolkata offers guests free internet access.
            The hotel features a concierge, room service, and 24 hour check-in. Plus, Pride Plaza Hotel Kolkata.
        </item>
        <item>
            Asia\'s first luxury hotel, The Lalit Great Eastern is a heritage landmark located in the main business and shopping district of Kolkata.
            Restored and renovated over a period of seven years, the hotel holds the distinction of being the longest continuously operating hotel for 165 years.
            Built in 1841 as Auckland Hotel, it has been referred to as the \'Jewel of the East\' and the \'Best Hotel East of the Suez\'.
            Over the years, the hotel has been the favourite haunt of royalty and celebrities from across the world.
        </item>
        <item>
            Welcome to JW Marriott Kolkata - a landmark of luxury in the east of India and a top choice among 5-star hotels in Kolkata.
            Towering over JBS Haldane Avenue just 6km from Netaji Subhash Chandra Bose Airport, our hotel is equidistant from the airport
            and the old central business district. JW Marriott Kolkata boasts 281 spacious rooms with state-of-the-art facilities.
            We are a premier choice among hotels in Kolkata due to our passion for personal service and our exemplary dining options.
            At JW Marriott Kolkata, guests enjoy a convenient location, impeccable restaurants, luxurious rooms and suites,
            and large event spaces that are suitable for corporate events, weddings, and other functions. Our hotel also provides a beautiful infinity pool,
            a fitness club, and a holistic Spa by JW.
        </item>

        <item>
            Hyatt Regency Kolkata is a luxury business hotel in Kolkata (or “Calcutta”), India.
            The hotel creates the feel of a private cocoon away from the complexities of modern living without giving up any of its luxuries.
            Hyatt Regency Kolkata is located next to Salt Lake Stadium &amp; 15 mins drive from IT hub and is a preferred business destination of East India.
            A tranquil retreat amid spectacular landscaped gardens, featuring 234 luxury guest rooms and suites,
            the hotel allows guests to relax and rejuvenate while staying in Kolkata.
        </item>

    </string-array>

    <!-- TODO: Name of the hospital -->
    <string-array name="name_of_the_hospital">
        <item>Fortis Hospital</item>
        <item>Medica Superspecialty Hospital</item>
        <item>Columbia Asia Hospital</item>
        <item>Bhagirathi Neotia Woman &amp; Child Care Centre</item>
        <item>Sri Aurobindo Seva Kendra</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- TODO: Address of the hospital -->
    <string-array name="address_of_the_hospital">

        <item>
            Plot No 730, E M Bypass,
            \nEast Kolkata Township,
            \nKolkata - 700107,
            \nNear Anandapur
        </item>
        <item>
            No 127, E.M Bypass, Mukundapur,
            \nKolkata - 700099,
            \nNear Cash and Carry,
            \nE M Bypass (Map)Hospitals
        </item>
        <item>
            IB 193, Salt Lake City Sector 5,
            \nKolkata - 700091,
            \nNear Saltlake Stadium (Map)Hospitals
        </item>
        <item>
            No 2, Rawdon Street, Circus Avenue, Kolkata - 700017,
            \nOpposite Assembly Of God Church School,
             \nMullick Bazar,
             \nPark Street (Map)Hospitals
        </item>
        <item>
            1 H, Gariahat Road South,
            \nJodhpur Park, Kolkata - 700068,
            \nNear Jadavpur Police Station (Map)
        </item>

    </string-array>

    <!-- TODO:Description of the hospital -->
    <string-array name="description_of_the_hospital">
        <item>
            Neurologists
            \nGynaecologist &amp; Obstetrician Doctors
            \nGastroenterologists
            \nOrthopaedic Doctors
            \nCardiologists
            \nPulmonologists Doctors
            \nNephrologists
        </item>
        <item>
            Neurologists
            \nGastroenterologists
            \nOrthopaedic Doctors
            \nCardiologists
            \nUrologist Doctors
        </item>
        <item>
            Gynaecologist &amp; Obstetrician Doctors
            \nDermatologists
            \nDiagnostic Centres
            \nGeneral Physician Doctors
        </item>
        <item>
            Neurologists
            \nGynaecologist &amp; Obstetrician Doctors
            \nGastroenterologists
            \nPaediatricians
            \nDermatologists
        </item>

        <item>
            Neurologists
            \nGynaecologist &amp; Obstetrician Doctors
            \nGastroenterologists
            \nPaediatricians
            \nDermatologists
        </item>

    </string-array>

    <!-- TODO: Name of the shoping malls -->
    <string-array name="name_of_the_mall">
        <item>Quest Mall</item>
        <item> South City Mall</item>
        <item>City Center</item>
        <item>Mani Square</item>
        <item>Acropolis Mall</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- TODO: Address of the shoping mall -->
    <string-array name="address_of_the_mall">

        <item>
            Location: Syed Amir Ali Ave
            \nTimings: 10 AM to 11 PM
        </item>
        <item>
            Location: Prince Anwar Shah Road
            \nTimings: 10 AM to 10 PM
        </item>
        <item>
            Location: Newtown
            \nTimings: 10 AM to 10 PM
        </item>
        <item>
            Location: Maniktala Main Road
            \nTimings: 10 AM to 10 PM
        </item>
        <item>
            Location: Rajdanga Main Rd
            \nTimings: 10 AM to 9 PM
        </item>

    </string-array>

    <!-- TODO:Description of the shoping mall -->
    <string-array name="description_of_the_mall">
        <item>
            The number of luxury stores such as Gucci, Armani, Burberry,
            \nRolex and many others is a big attraction for shoppers of this mall.
             \nOther than this, there are various other clothing stores
            \nas well where you can shop at a much affordable price.
        </item>
        <item>
            At South City Mall, you can find almost all the famous regular brands
            \nwhich include Guess, Jack and Jones, Lacoste, Vero Moda, and many more.
             \nStores like Shoppers Stop and Pantaloons can be seen in this mall
             \nwhere you can find the number of brands. Timezone, a gaming zone
            \nfor hours of entertainment can also be spotted here for unlimited fun.

        </item>
        <item>
            This is one of the most famous malls in Kolkata where shoppers of all ages
            \nwould love to spend a number of hours. This is a huge mall divided into different
            \nsections which include, a shopping plaza, an entertainment zone,
            \nfood court, cineplex, and different other 240 stores.

        </item>
        <item>
            Another fine destination for shoppers, Mani Square offers almost everything
            \nyou want to see while exploring a market. Whether it is about clothing,
             \ngaming or eateries, the place has it all for the visitors.
             \nFamous brands like Adidas, Levi’s, Raymond’s, Tissot, and much more,
             \nattracts the attention of many visitors throughout the day.
        </item>

        <item>
            If you are in this city and want to explore different malls in Kolkata,
            \nthen Acropolis Mall should be on your list of must-visit malls.
            \nThe luxurious ambiance of the mall raised many eyebrows of first-time visitors.
            \nThis mall has 5 floors where you can find all the popular brands to fill the shopping bags.
             \nThe large food court and fine ding is another popular area you will see while taking a break from shopping.
        </item>

    </string-array>


</resources>
